=Deity Of Love= =Episode 11=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 11 =
Are sure you are fine?
هل أنت متأكد أنك بخير؟
How about I fetch you a doctor?
ما رأيك أن أحضر لك طبيب؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
I will be alright when I stare at you.
سأكون بخير عندما أحدق فيك.
- Really? - Sure.
- حقًا؟  - بالتأكيد.
Well, then lie down and rest.
حسنًا ، ثم استلق واسترح.
Does your hand hurt?
هل يدك تؤلمك؟
How about I blow it for you?
ماذا لو أنفخها لك؟
It is useless whether it hurts or not.
من غير المجدي أن يؤلم أم لا.
Brother won't drink the medicine anyway.
لن يشرب الأخ الدواء على أي حال.
The herbs have been boiled or nothing again.
تم غلي الأعشاب أو لا شيء مرة أخرى.
How could it be in vain?
كيف يمكن أن يكون عبثا؟
It tastes great.
طعمها رائع.
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
Medicines don't taste good.
الأدوية ليس لها مذاق جيد.
As long as they are boiled by you,
ما دمت مسلوقة بواسطتك ،
they taste sweet in my heart.
طعمها حلو في قلبي.
They are pretending to be husband and wife.
إنهم يتظاهرون بأنهم زوج وزوجة.
Why does Brother treat her so well?
لماذا يعاملها الاخ جيدا؟
Oh.
أوه.
So it's an impersonation.
لذا فهو انتحال للهوية.
Then I can pursue Miss Xiaoqing again.
ثم يمكنني متابعة الآنسة شياو تشينغ مرة أخرى.
Ah.
آه.
Miss Xiaoqing.
ملكة جمال شياو تشينغ.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
This is especially for Miss Xiaoqing.
هذا بشكل خاص للآنسة شياو تشينغ.
The flowers and jewelry I fetched.
الزهور والمجوهرات التي جلبتها.
Alas.
واحسرتاه.
This one.
هذا.
It's from Spiritual Jade Pavilion.
إنه من Spiritual Jade Pavilion.
This is from Frost Flowers Pavilion…
هذا من فروست فلاور بافيليون ...
These all are…
هذه كلها ...
Ouch.
أوتش.
Oh my.
يا بلادي.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
No big deal.
ليس مهما.
It might be some minor injuries.
قد تكون بعض الإصابات الطفيفة.
Back and leg pain.
آلام الظهر والساق.
Let me get you some medicines.
دعني أحضر لك بعض الأدوية.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Let's go somewhere less crowded.
لنذهب إلى مكان أقل ازدحامًا.
Hey, Miss Xiaoqing.
يا آنسة شياو تشينغ.
He's pretending to be ill.
إنه يتظاهر بأنه مريض.
I don't like what you send me.
لا يعجبني ما ترسله لي.
Such a decisive girl.
يا لها من فتاة حاسمة.
My crush on you gets stronger.
إعجابي بك يصبح أقوى.
There is nothing in the world that I can't buy.
لا يوجد شيء في العالم لا أستطيع شراؤه.
Miss Xiaoqing, you will be my girl.
آنسة شياو تشينغ ، ستكونين فتاتي.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)